<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opportunities | Academic CV Pro Hugo Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/opportunities/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/opportunities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Opportunities</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu7a6250c5a15096aebb6a54d272ade87d_8264_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Opportunities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/opportunities/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/opportunities/opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/opportunities/opportunities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;openings&#34;&gt;Openings&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for talented, curious, and highly-motivated students and postdocs to join us! This is a great opportunities for young scholars to join one of the most exciting research fields that could potentially change our lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;postdoctoral-scholars&#34;&gt;Postdoctoral scholars&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Position available. The position is set to start as soon as fall 2024. We seek outstanding individuals with strong demonstrated skills in at least one of the following fields:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimental quantum science and engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acoustics/MEMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nanofabrication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Applicants should submit a CV, a brief statement of research interests and goals, and contact information of at least two references. Please send these materials to chenmo AT caltech DOT edu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;graduate-students&#34;&gt;Graduate students&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for motivated PhD students from MSE, ECE, Physics, MechE, Applied Physics, and other relevant fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prospective PhD students are encouraged to reach out to Prof. Chen with your CV and a brief statement of your research interests and goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current UW PhD students interested in our lab are encouraged to contact Prof. Chen with your CV and a brief statement of your research interests and goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;undergraduate-researchers&#34;&gt;Undergraduate researchers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We enthusiastically promote undergraduate research through summer projects and/or independent research. Please reach out to Prof. Chen with your CV and a brief description of your research interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mo Chen, Assistant Professor of MSE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:chenmo@caltech.edu&#34;&gt;chenmo AT caltech DOT edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(xxx)-xxx-xxxx&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Office:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;visiting&#34;&gt;Visiting&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our offices are located in the Roberts Hall (ROB) on the beautiful campus of University of Washington. Our lab is next door in Roberts Hall.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
